https://www.yescoloring.com/privacy-policy.html

YesColoring
Menu
Dec 06
'20
Slide Crayon!
Autos - Vehicle Rides:Mega CarsHard Driving TrucksMighty MotorcyclesStupendous Dirtbikes-ATVTransportation
YesColoring Blog:Coloring Pages Free BLOG!
ABCs - Education:Awesome Alphabets - GraffitiSmooth Clocks Tell TimeSuper
Private PlanesSpectacular
Space ShuttlesBattleships - Aircraft CarriersSmooth Ships BoatsHigh Seas Pirate ShipsTrains
Bible:Faithful Bible Christian
Construction - Tractors:Rock Hard ConstructionRugged Farm Tractors
Cartoons - Pokemon - MarioPowerhouse PokemonAmazing Super MarioTenacious TransformersFamous Star WarsIce Cold Xbox Halo 543 ReachBlack Hearted
PiratesCowboysHeroic Cartoons HQ
Holidays:Regal - Fun Christmas!Wonderful EasterValentines4th of JulyFathers DadMothers DayBountiful ThanksgivingHoliday AlphabetsHappy Holidays Headquarters
I Love Daddy - MamaI Love DaddyI Love Mama
Musical Instruments:Musical Headquarters
Sports:Spectacular Sports HQ
USA - World:Patriotic America HeadquartersHigh Flying Flags USA WorldFlowers USA - World - ExoticEarthy Maps USA
Odds & Ends:Grand Geometric ColoringBlockbuster Hollywood StarsWhat Boys KnowHow Color WorkHow Crayons WorkRemove Crayon WaxMake Stencils TemplatesMake Coloring BooksAbout UsLink To YesColoringPrint -
Resize HelpHOME YesColoring Coloring Pages FreeSwift Sitemap SearchCowboysFootball -NFLJuggler Soccer Coloring
Searching? Enter Its Name. Searching For A Coloring Page?Add Words: Coloring or Printable. Example: Porsche Coloring
YesColoring Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy for YesColoring.com website. YesColoring allow ads to support your coloring pages free
website.
At YesColoring.com we are dedicated to protecting your data and privacy.
We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use YesColoring.com, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. This will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.
YesColoring.com strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.
About Our Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that YesColoring.com stores on your computer, which your browser provides to YesColoring.com each time you return to the site. We use cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their use of our website, and their website access preferences.
Google Analytics Cookies
YesColoring.com uses Google Analytics to analyze the use of this website. Google Analytics collects demographic and interest data, and generates statistical and other information about website use, by means of cookies. These cookies are kept on your computer. We share this information with Google, which will store and use this information on its servers.
Google's privacy policy is available at: https://policies.google.com/privacy
YesColoring.com uses information from Google Analytics to track the number of visits to the website, browsers and operating systems. No personally identifiable information is obtained from these cookies. We use the information that Google Analytics generates relating to our website to create reports about the use of the site. These reports allow us to update the site and improve your usage of it.
If you do not wish your data to be collected via Google Analytics, you can install its opt-out browser extension or add-on... https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/]
Advertising Cookies
Some third-party advertisements are served by Google. Google's cookie enables it to serve ads to our visitors based on their visits to other sites on the Web. You may opt out of personalized ads by visiting the Google ad opt-out page
This link from Google provides more information about how Google manages data in its ad products: How Google Uses Information From Sites Or Apps That Use Our Services
Refusing Cookies
You can set your browser to accept or refuse all cookies automatically, or notify you when a cookie is being requested. Taking this action should not cause a problem with the continued use of our site. Consult the Help section of your browser for guidance on how to refuse all cookies or to notify you when a cookie is requested.
If you choose to refuse YesColoring.com's cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.
California Consumer Privacy Act Statement
YesColoring.com has not sold any personal information from visitors to the site in the past 12 months.
Personally Identifiable Information
YesColoring.com may collect and use your personal information for the following purposes:
To run and operate our site.
To display content on the site correctly.
To improve customer service.
To help us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
To personalize your user experience.
To understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our site.
To improve our site.
To improve our products and services.
To run a promotion, contest, survey or other site feature.
To send information to you that you agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to you.
To send periodic emails, which may include electronic newsletters and/or autoresponder series of emails.
To respond to your enquiries, questions, and/or other requests.
YesColoring.com may collect personally identifiable information from you in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when you visit our site, register on the site, or fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our site.
This site lets you share content with your friends and followers on various social media platforms. Below are links to the privacy policies of...
Facebook Privacy Policy
Pinterest Privacy Policy
Twitter Privacy Policy
AddThis Privacy Policy
YesColoring.com may uses Facebook commenting. Facebook stores all of your comments and may show them on your timeline, depending on your Facebook settings.
Privacy PolicyYesColoring.com offers RSS as a way to easily follow content updates. We use FeedBlitz Privacy Policy to let you subscribe to these updates via your email address.
We also provide links for easy access to My Yahoo! Privacy Policy and Feedly Privacy Policy. Before you choose to use either as your RSS reader, review its privacy policy.
You can always refuse to supply personally identifiable information and visit our site anonymously. However, it may prevent you from engaging in certain site-related activities.
If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information, we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. We will use personal information received from you for internal purposes only and will not sell it or provide it to third parties.
We also collect each visitor's IP address, which helps us combat spam and fraud. We do not use IP addresses for any other purpose.
YesColoring.com contains links to other websites that may be of interest to you. However, once you have used them to leave our site, we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information you provide while visiting such sites. These sites are not governed by this privacy statement.
Always exercise caution by reviewing the privacy statement of the website in question before continuing to use it.
Non-personally Identifiable Information
We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you whenever you interact with our site. Non-personally identifiable information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about your method of connecting to our site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider you used, and other similar information.
Children's Privacy Protection
We do not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from anyone under 16 years of age.
Release of Information
If we sell YesColoring.com, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale so that the service provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make.
Data Storage
Personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information collected by this site
is stored on our host's servers. That host is SiteSell Inc., located at 1000 Saint-Jean Boulevard, Suite 702, Pointe-Claire, QC H9R 5P1 Canada.
How You Can Correct or Remove Information
We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personally identifiable information. If you have submitted personally identifiable information through our website and would like to download and review that information. You can also request to edit or delete any of your information from the servers click on this link
Updates and Effective Date
YesColoring.com reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our cookie and privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that those practices have changed and provide a link to the updated privacy policy.
We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.
Agreeing to Terms
If you do not agree to YesColoring.com's privacy policy as posted here on this website, please do not consent to the setting of cookies and the collection and storage of your personally identifiable information.
Your explicit consent indicates acceptance of this privacy policy in its entirety.
Last updated: November 18 2020
ADVERTISEMENT
UptoTop: Privacy Policy
Coloring Pages Free Blog At YesColoring - 4Yo'Eyeballs2C!
HOMEPAGE: YES COLORING
Swift Sitemap Search Short Cuts
AA AL
AM AZ
B
CA CN
CO CZ
D E
V W X Y Z
Thank You For Visiting and Hanging With YesColoring Coloring Pages Free For All.
Coloring Pages Blog! Subscribe!
Rowdy Pokemon Moon Coloring: Toxapex 748 - Mimikyu 778 At YesColoring Dec 10, 20 05:10 PMBrawler Pokemon Moon Coloring Pictures. Your Generation 7 Pokemon Continue With These Second Of Three Sets Of Sun and Moon. Free Coloring pages to print of Toxapex 748! Mudbray 749! Mudsdale 750! Dewp… Read More
Nativity Christmas Coloring Pictures | Shepherds | Jesus | Mary Dec 10, 20 11:15 AMSolemn Christmas Coloring Pictures - who else desires them?! This Christmas holiday print out your Christmas coloring pages of Jesus, Mary, Wise Men, Manger, Shepards, Angels of the Lord... Read More
YesColoring Coloring Pages Free | Popular 'N Fired Up!| Come Over Now! Dec 09, 20 06:53 PMKids - Boys, These Are Your Great Coloring Pages Free at Yes Coloring. You Have 45 Categories And 1000s Of Coloring Sheets To Color In. These Safe Coloring Sheets Are Hard 'N Easy Printables, And Clas… Read More
Christmas Coloring Sheets 12 Days Of Christmas | Free | Kids Christmas Dec 09, 20 12:44 PM Print Out Your Christmas Coloring Sheets Of Partridge, Doves, Lords A Leapin', 'n Drummer Boys, Too! Now, Learn Your Twelve Days of Christmas Song Lyrics. Sing Out Loud!... Read More
COOLEST BLOG! COLORING PAGES FREE "Wow!"
Get Free Coloring Updates Via RSS
Week Dec 06 '20
Happy Birthday December Born Coloring Kids!
All Time Favorites! "Whoo Wee!":
Christmas Wow!
Make Stencils Templates!
Make Coloring Books!
Print - Resize Help!
COLORING PAGES FREE CATEGORIES!
Autos - Vehicle Rides:
ABCs - Education:
Thanksgiving Alphabet
Alphabets - Graffiti
Clocks Tell Time
Sign Languages
Army:
Army - Air Force
Navy
Aircraft - Ships - Trains:
Bible:
Bible Christian
Cartoons:
Construction - Tractors:
Construction
Farm Tractors
Holidays:
Musical Instruments:
Drums
Guitars
Pianos
Musical HQ
Sports:
USA - World:
Odds and Ends:
Coloring Pages Free Blog!
Sitemap Search
Official Website
EyeBall Your COLORING PAGES FREE BLOG!
Swift Sitemap Search
Official YesColoring Coloring Pages Free!
Privacy Policy for YesColoring Coloring Pages Free...
SAFE Free: Click Red Menu Or Pictures For Coloring Pages Free
© 2021 YesColoring.com by Michael Bennett (Coloring Buddy Mike) Trademarks/Trade Names/Copyrights Are Properties Of Their Respective Owners
Home - Coloring Pages Free Blog! - Privacy Policy
Contact - Swift Sitemap - About Us - Link To YesColoring
